adaptnetwork.com 2016-06-06

# Privacy Policy | ADAPT Network

This Privacy Policy (“Policy” or “Privacy Policy”) forms part of the Terms of Use (“TOU” or “Terms of Use”) for the access and use of this Website and should be read in conjunction with the TOU. ADAPT Network (“ADAPT Network”, “ADAPT”, “we”, “us” or “our”) is strongly committed to protecting your privacy and providing a safe online experience for all of our users while offering the highest quality Content and services to them. This Privacy Policy discloses what information we gather, how we use it, to whom we disclose personal information and other information you have provided, and how to correct or change personal information that you have provided to us.

This Privacy Policy applies to ADAPT Network. We urge you to read the complete Privacy Policy set forth below along with our cookie policy, as well as our Terms of Use, and contact us if you have any questions. Use of this site constitutes your agreement to be bound by and adhere to the terms of this Policy and Terms of Use.

 **1\. Information Collection by us**

Personal Information. We collect personally identifiable information, such as names, mailing addresses, e-mail addresses, demographic information, and similar information in a variety of situations, including but not limited to the following: (i) when you subscribe to one of our newsletters or place an order (see the section below for more information on ordering); (ii) when you register at one of our websites in connection with the purchase of a product, publication, or service; (iii) when you enter personal information on one of our websites as a condition of participating in contests, promotions, or sweepstakes offered via these websites; or (iv) when you wish to have a product or service fulfilled by a fulfilment partner who can meet the continuing needs of our customers.

 **Ordering:**  
When you order from us, we collect personally identifiable information from you. If you order one of our products or services, we will collect and maintain your name, e-mail address, billing address, shipping address, telephone number, product selections, credit card or other payment information, order number, referring URL, IP address, page you bought from and a password. We collect this, and other information, as disclosed in this Policy, in order to fill your order, to communicate with you about your order and to send you promotional materials. Before confirming your order, you will have the opportunity to review the product order form and make changes and additions to the information it contained and these changes will be automatically kept for future use.  
Information Collected Automatically. Our websites automatically collect certain information, such as your IP address, browser type, domain name, access times and referring website address. This helps facilitate your online experience at our websites. See Sections 4 and 5 of this Privacy Policy for more detail on cookies, web beacons, and other information collected automatically by our websites.

 **2\. How we use your information**

We use the personal information you provide to allow you to make product purchases, to fulfil your requests, improve our Content, products and services, to send you promotional offers related to ADAPT Network or our business partners, and to operate our business. A user may, at any time, opt out of receiving promotional offers by mail or e-mail (see Section 7 for information on controlling your personal information). We also use collected information to evaluate and administer our products and services, respond to any problems that may arise, such as product delivery failures, difficulties in navigating our sites or accessing certain features, as well as to gauge user trends to determine what products and services are most popular with users, and to put you in touch with fulfilment partners who can provide services that we cannot. We allow users of our website to send articles or links by e-mail to other parties who may be interested in them. We do not retain any e-mail addresses of either the sender or recipient of such articles or links after they are sent, and do not share these e-mail addresses with third parties.

 **3\. Disclosing Your Information**

We will not disclose your personal information to any other party other than in accordance with this Privacy Policy and as described below:

Sharing Within the ADAPT Family. We may provide personally identifiable information and non-personally-identifiable information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies, or other businesses or persons for the purpose of processing such information on our behalf. We require that these parties agree to process such information in compliance with our Policy, and we use reasonable efforts to limit their use of such information and to use other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.  
ADAPT’s Service Providers. ADAPT Network may decide to share your personal information with companies that work on behalf of or with ADAPT. These companies may use your personal information to inform you about ADAPT’s products and services, to provide you with information about other exciting products and services, or otherwise to assist ADAPT in serving its customers, understanding its consumer market, or devising effective marketing strategies to reach more consumers.

Anonymous elements of your personal information. We may share information that is not personally identifiable (such as anonymous User usage data) with interested third-parties to assist them in understanding the usage patterns for certain content, services, advertisements, promotions, and/or functionality on our Website.

Credit Card Companies; Third Party Payment Services; Third Party Promotional Sites. As in any transaction, your credit card company will have all relevant information about the name of the vendor, item(s) purchased, and date and total cost. ADAPT Network will not otherwise provide any personal data to your credit card company. In some cases, we use third party payment and transaction services to facilitate your transactions and process your orders. In such cases, we will share your personal information and credit card information with the third party payment services solely for the purpose of completing the transaction or processing your order.  
Public Postings. You should be aware that if you voluntarily disclose information, personal or otherwise, online in any community area (whether through ADAPT websites or any other service available online), that information can be collected and used by others. Accordingly, you should use caution when sharing any personal information with others in any community area (whether through ADAPT websites or any other service available online).

Required Disclosures of Information. We reserve the right to use or disclose any information without notice or consent as needed to satisfy any law, regulation or legal request; to conduct investigations of consumer complaints or possible breaches of law; to protect the integrity of our sites and our property and assure adherence to our terms of use; to protect the safety of our visitors or others; to fulfil your requests; or to cooperate in any legal investigation or process.  
Changes in Corporate Structure. In developing our business, we might sell certain assets, or the business, or parts of it, may be sold, merged or otherwise transferred. In such transactions, user information, whether personally identifiable or otherwise, may be one of the transferred assets.

 **4\. Our use of cookies and other information gathering technologies**

Your Web browser offers “cookies” which, if you allow their use, store small amounts of data on your computer when you visit a website. Cookies do not contain any personally identifiable information about you and therefore cannot be used to identify you personally. Cookies assist us in tracking which of our features you like best, and also enable us to customize our content according to your preferences. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies by modifying your browser and our websites are viewable even if you disable the cookie function on your browser. However, if you disable cookies, some advanced and customized features or offerings on our site will not be available to you.

Additionally, we use third-party companies to collect non-personally identifiable information (e.g., the pages you visit, and which links you click, which ads you see and click on, and the categories of search terms you enter) when you visit one of our websites. Some of these third-party companies collect information when serving ads on our sites, while others collect information without showing ads on our sites. These companies may use the information outlined above (which does not include your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to our sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. These companies often use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information.

Read more about our use of cookies on our [cookie policy](http://www.adaptnetwork.com/privacy-policy/cookie-policy/ "Cookie Policy").

We may also employ the use of other technologies to track the online usage pattern of our Users in our website but such tracking will not be personally identifiable.

 **5\. Third Party Advertisers**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our websites. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

We use our own ad server, as a primary ad server, running the Revive Adserver software ([http://www.revive-adserver.com](http://www.revive-adserver.com/)) to serve ad tags to our websites. We may also use DoubleClick as a third party ad server. If you would like to know more about their information gathering practices and “opt-out” procedures, please see <http://www.doubleclick.com/us/corporate/privacy>.

 **6\. Controlling Your Personal Information?**

We believe that choice in how and when you are contacted is key to customer satisfaction, so we offer several ways for you to update your contact information, change your preferences, or opt out of receiving future communications.  
a) If you have an online account at one of our websites, you may be able to log on and update or change your contact or account information. Check the site for further information.  
b) You may unsubscribe to any of our online e-mail updates or newsletters by following the unsubscribe instructions in the body of any e-mail message.  
c) You may also contact us at info@adaptnetwork.com for any inquiry or request regarding our privacy policy or the handling of your personal information. If you have opted out of receiving future e-mails from us, we will implement your opt-out request within 10 business days of receiving the opt-out request.

 **7\. Updating your details**

If any of the details you have provided to us change, then it is your responsibility to inform us of any such changes.

 **8\. Protection of your information**

 **Our security:**  
The internet is not a secure medium. We have, however, put in place various security procedures to help to protect your personal information. Protection technologies we use include industry recognised firewalls, browser certification, password protection and limited access to personal information. Your personal information may also be protected by the password you created when you registered at one of our websites where this feature is offered. The confidentiality of any password is yours to protect. You may change it anytime by following the instructions at the website where you registered.

 **Confidentiality:**  
We keep your personal information confidential. Our internal procedures cover the storage, access and disclosure of your information.

 **Imperfect security:**  
We do not represent, warrant or guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us, and any transmission is carried out at your sole risk. Once we receive information we have our own security systems in place, but we do not represent or warrant or guarantee that such systems cannot be breached. Although we will take steps to protect your personal details and you have some options to limit these no security measures are perfect and we cannot promise that only authorised people will access your personal information

 **Breach of security:**  
If our security systems have been breached, then we will take appropriate steps to remedy this and to notify you of any breach.

 **9\. Children’s Privacy**

This site or any other ADAPT website is not directed to Users who are under the age of thirteen (13) but may include features or material that may be appealing to children under the age of 13. ADAPT is strongly committed to protecting the safety and privacy of children who visit our websites. We do not knowingly collect personal information online from children under 13. Some of our sites may include chat rooms, bulletin boards and other features that we believe are unsuitable for children under 13 and which are not necessarily monitored. We encourage all parents to talk to their kids about online safety and to monitor their children’s use of the Internet.

 **10\. Third Parties And Links**

In the event that you provide personal information to any third party via any ADAPT website or any offer made available to you by ADAPT Network, you understand that ADAPT Network is not responsible for such third parties’ use or misuse of your personal information. You should review the privacy and information sharing practices of such third parties. Additionally, ADAPT Network may offer links to or from websites it controls to other sites within the ADAPT family as well as to sites operated by third parties. We offer links to third party sites so that you can conveniently visit our vendors and advertisers or locate other content likely to be of interest. We are not responsible for the content, practices or policies of sites operated by third parties and urge you to inquire about them before providing any personally-identifiable information.

 **11\. Acceptance Of These Terms; Changes To Our Privacy Policy**

By using any of our sites and providing us with your information, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, you should not use or access any of our sites. Additionally, this Privacy Policy incorporates all of the terms, conditions, and provisions of the ADAPT Terms of Use, which are posted on our sites. If you do not agree with the ADAPT Terms of Use, you should not use or access any of our sites.

We will occasionally update this Privacy Policy as necessary to protect our users and to comply with a changing environment. We will indicate at the bottom of this page the date the Policy was last amended. We recommend that you check the posted Privacy Policy when you visit any of our sites to be sure you are aware of and understand our current policy. Your continued use of the respective site means you accept the updated Privacy Policy.

 **12\. Contact Information**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our privacy practices, please e-mail us at info@adaptnetwork.com. Please include the URL of the website involved in your request.

Last Update May 17th, 2016
